inetlinkexchange.com 2009-06-08

# Free Link Exchange Directory

**InetLinkExchange.com Privacy Policy:**

**What This Privacy Policy Covers:  
\--------------------------------------------- **  
This policy covers how InetLinkExchange.com treats personal information that InetLinkExchange.com collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that InetLinkExchange.com does not own or control, or to people that InetLinkExchange.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use:  
\------------------------------------------- **  
InetLinkExchange.com collects personal information when you sign up to use InetLinkExchange.com services. 

When you sign up we ask for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with InetLinkExchange.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

InetLinkExchange.com collects information about your transactions with us and uses them in aggregate for statistical purposes and identifying trends. 

InetLinkExchange.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, InetLinkExchange.com cookie information, and the page you request.

InetLinkExchange.com uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for our services (link trades with potential partners), improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal purposes. Email addresses are never made public on InetLinkExchange.com. However, your "contact name" is made available through the Service.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure:  
\------------------------------------------------- **  
InetLinkExchange.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies, period. Email addresses are never exposed or shared on InetLinkExchange.com. InetLinkExchange.com acts as the messenger between sites wanting to trade links.

**Third Party Advertising:  
\--------------------------------- **  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Cookies:  
\------------ **  
InetLinkExchange.com sets and accesses InetLinkExchange.com cookies for login/authentication purposes only. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information:  
\------------------------------------------------------------------------------- **  
You can review, edit, or delete your InetLinkExchange.com account information at any time. 

You can delete your InetLinkExchange.com account by visiting our Account Administration pages. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the InetLinkExchange.com service, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your InetLinkExchange.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

**Confidentiality and Security:  
\-------------------------------------- **  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:  
\------------------------------------------ **  
InetLinkExchange.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your InetLinkExchange.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**InetLinkExchange.com.  
**   
Effective Date: June 1, 2009
